Your case is already closed, right?
Closed as an accident.
You orchestrated these accidents.
Because you knew that
if you called the police,
Mu Weijie would lash out.
But if you killed him yourself,
you would be punished by the law.
So,
you orchestrated all these accidents.
I pulled off an accident.
I'm so amazing.
Where is the evidence?
I don't think I'm that capable.
Of course you are.
The final determined cause of death for Mu Weijie
was an overdose of aphrodisiacs,
which led to sudden cardiac death.
So what you had to do,
as the first step,
all you had to do was wait,
wait for him to let his guard down.
Wait until he trusts you completely.
Can you take a look for me?
We're out of tape.
Does anyone have extra?
There's some in the teacher's office.
I'll get it for you.
Thanks.
It's like this.
Mu Weijie's office has no surveillance
or door lock.
Plus, you saw him taking his medicine.
So,
as long as the timing is right,
you could easily get that bottle of medicine
and take a few pills out.
Step two.
You took these pills
to the university chemistry lab.
You took applied chemistry as an elective in college,
so you took full advantage of that.
You took the powder from these pills,
recrystallized and refined it,
and put it back into a capsule.
At this concentration,
it's dangerous for a normal man to take,
let alone someone with heart problems.
My colleagues checked.
The female student in the studio who took the applied chemistry course.
You were the only one.
So I conclude
that you
are the killer.
Unfortunately,
the chemistry lab is used every day,
so all traces are long gone.
Sound logic.
Good theory.
But how can you be so sure
I could make him take that high-concentration pill that day?
That's your most brilliant move.
You didn't need to guarantee when he would take the pill.
Because Mu Weijie would continue to demand sex from you.
You knew
this pill,
he would take it sooner or later.
To accelerate this outcome,
you stopped at nothing.
No matter how much you despised and hated him,
you still chose to actively cater to him,
so he would take that pill sooner.
Over here.
My Danaë
has finally figured it out.
But your carefully designed script
ultimately
harmed your friend.
Mu Weijie was originally going to find you that day.
But he saw Lin Rongrong returning instead.
Unknowingly,
that pill had already taken effect.
His blood began to rush.
[Breathing heavily]
Due to the high concentration,
his consciousness began to blur,
and he gradually lost his reason.
Mr. Mu, you can't do this.
Mr. Mu!
What a perfect story.
It's as if you saw it with your own eyes.
What a pity.
You still have no evidence.
I will listen to the police
and stay here for a full 24 hours.
However,
within these 24 hours,
if you can't find any evidence,
we might never see each other again.
Hey.
Ms. Zhuang had us stake out here all day.
Lin Rongrong hasn't made a peep.
What do you think she's doing in her room?
The curtains are drawn.
Is she going to sleep at this hour?
I don't think so.
If you hadn't thrown yourself at my husband and seduced him,
why would he have chosen you?
Recently, news of a young art teacher
passing away unexpectedly has attracted widespread attention.
It's not like that. It's not like that.
I'm obviously the victim here.
What's going on?
Oh no.
Lin Rongrong.
To the hospital. To the hospital.
Drive.
Brother, I'll go get the car.
Lin Rongrong.
Hello?
Lao Fang, say that again.
Captain Zhuang, I'm at Mancheng Hospital now.
Come quickly.
Lin Rongrong committed suicide.
You and Xiaobai wait at the hospital.
Lin Rongrong can't die.
I'll be right there.
Take me to see her.
Just let me see her,
and I'll give you a satisfactory answer.
How is it? What's the situation now?
How is Rongrong?
Fortunately, she was brought in just in time.
After emergency treatment,
she is out of danger.
But the patient's condition is not very good.
If possible,
please keep as quiet as you can.
Ask whatever you want to ask quickly.
Let me in.
Officer Zhuang,
I beg you.
Please let me in
to see Rongrong.
Please.
Xiaoyue.
Why did you try to commit suicide?
Answer me. Why did you try to commit suicide?
What would I do if you died?
Xiaoyue.
I'm sorry.
I was so stupid.
But I really didn't know what to do.
Does it hurt?
I'm sorry.
This is all because of me.
I failed to protect you.
How could that be, Xiaoyue?
You got involved in this mess because of me.
I'm really sorry.
I really didn't expect Mu Weijie to do that to you.
It's all my fault.
Stop talking nonsense.
We are the victims.
Qiaoyue,
I will never blame you.
You are my best friend.
Since we were kids,
every time I was wronged,
you were always the first to be by my side.
We promised to be together forever.
I'll go wherever you go.
I'm sorry.
I chickened out this time.
Rongrong.
Recover well.
Live well.
It's all in the past now.
I will protect you.
Wait for me.
Officer Zhuang.
I plead guilty.